buzzdock.com 2011-06-29

# Buzzdock | Privacy Policy

Buzzdock LLC respects the privacy of its users and non-users. This privacy policy discloses any information we obtain and how we use it. Buzzdock also goes to great lengths to ensure that the information and content that users add to our system is secure and only accessible to intended users. Buzzdock may modify this policy from time to time, and the changes will be posted here. 

## 1\. What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you use a Buzzdock service, register on our site or enter a contest. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. 

## 2\. What do we use your information for?

**Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:**

To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs) 

To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature

To send periodic emails

The email address you provide for order processing may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your user account, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. 

**Note:** If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email. 

## 3\. How we protect your information

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you access your personal information. 

## 4\. Browser Cookies

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business. 

## 5\. Buzzdock Information Disclosures

**Buzzdock reserves the rights to disclose personally-identifiable information in the following cases:**

To respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal processes. Or to establish and exercise our legal rights to defend against legal claims; 

If Buzzdock is acquired by or merged with another company, we might transfer your personal and non-personal information to that company. When this happens, Buzzdock will notify you before any information is transferred.

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you use Buzzdock services or visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [www.networkadvertising.org.](http://www.networkadvertising.org/)

## 6\. Performance Policy

Buzzdock does not guarantee error-free performance. Buzzdock will always try its best to protect its user and data privacy; however, it may not catch all unintended privacy issues. Buzzdock is not responsible for any damages, including incidental, consequential, or punitive damages, relating to the practices described in this policy. 

**Third party links**  
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites. 

California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent. 

Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance 

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older. 

## 7\. Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline. 

## 8\. Acceptance of Privacy Policy

This privacy policy is incorporated into and subject to Buzzdock's  Terms of Service. Use of Buzzdock services is subject to your compliance with those terms and conditions, which constitute a legal agreement between you and Buzzdock, Inc. THE USE OF THIS WEB SITE AND BUZZDOCK'S APPLICATIONS CONSTITUTES THE ACCEPTANCE OF BOTH TERMS OF SERVICE AND PRIVACY POLICY AGREEMENTS. If you do not agree with the terms and conditions of either document, please discontinue using any of Buzzdock’s services. 

## 9\. Yontoo Layers Information Collection and Transfer

To provide services to the User, Buzzdock requires Yontoo Layers software to be installed. Yontoo is a browser plugin platform that enables application developers to build browser applications such as Buzzdock.

When you install Yontoo Layers a set of non-personally identifiable values are stored on your computer and transferred back and stored on Yontoo's servers. This set of data consists of a randomly generated value that identifies the Yontoo Plug-in associated with each of your Yontoo supported browsers, and a randomly generated value representing your computer. These non-personally identifiable values enable Yontoo to provide you with the services and Layer Apps that you have selected to enable.

Once you have installed Yontoo Layers, each time you load or refresh a page in one of the Yontoo supported browsers, a request will be made to a Yontoo owned server to determine whether or not you have enabled any Services for the domain you are currently browsing. To determine this, the request made by Yontoo Layers will collect and pass back the following non-personally identifiable information: The unique identifier representing the Yontoo Layers plug-in installed in your browser and the URL representing the domain and page you are currently browsing. This data is used for the sole purpose of determining whether or not you have enabled any Layer Apps for the given domain and page. This Web usage information is never stored on Yontoo's servers.

If you utilize one of the Layer Apps that runs on the Facebook domain, Yontoo may also collect your Facebook username and user ID. This information will be stored in a cookie on your computer, and passed back as part of the aforementioned request. The sole purpose of this additional information is to provide you with a more personalized experience while utilizing Facebook related Layer Apps. This information will be stored on Yontoo's servers and is correlated with the above-mentioned Yontoo plug-in identifier.

No information from children under age 13. If you are under age 13, please do not attempt to register for Yontoo Layers or provide any personal information about yourself to Yontoo. If Yontoo learns that they have collected personal information from a child under age 13, they will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that Yontoo might have any information from a child under age 13, please contact Yontoo through its support page (<http://www.yontoo.com/Support.aspx>).

Parental participation: Yontoo strongly recommends that minors ask their parents for permission before sending any information about themselves to anyone over the Internet and we encourage parents to teach their children about safe internet use practices.

This information collection, transfer and storage as described in this section, is required for Yontoo Layers functionality. If you do not wish for any of this information to be collected or potentially shared as described in the following section (Yontoo Layers Information Sharing), you should not use the Yontoo Software or Services.

## 10\. Yontoo Layers Information Sharing

Yontoo may collect and analyze your usage patterns such as which sites you visit, that are not personally identifiable. These non-personally identifiable data are used to improve Yontoo's services, and may be shared with third parties. 

Yontoo Layers may engage with third party analytics providers, such as Google Analytics, to provide Yontoo with data to improve its software and services. Any information, such as URL visited, that Yontoo provides to one of these third parties is not personally identifiable. 

Yontoo reserves the right to track and use aggregate information about users of Yontoo Layers, such as operating system, browser type and locality, for a variety of purposes. Such aggregate information does not identify individual consumers. We may share such aggregate and related demographic information with third parties. 

## 11\. Yontoo Layers Privacy Policy

Yontoo respects the privacy of its users and non-users. Yontoo goes to great lengths to ensure that the information collected by Yontoo Layers is secure and only accessible by intended users. Yontoo may modify this policy from time to time, and the changes will be posted on the Yontoo website (<http://www.yontoo.com/PrivacyPolicy.aspx>). 

## 12\. For More Information

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. 

Buzzdock LLC  
5857 Owens Avenue, Suite 300  
Carlsbad, CA 92008  
Email: [legal@buzzdock.com](mailto:legal@buzzdock.com)  
Web form
